(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-27T00:04:21.544335",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
んなあああ！
Nnaaaa!
みんな、おるゅ〜？
Is everyone here~?
なのなのら！
Nano nanora!
絶対忠誠♡なのなのら！
Absolute loyalty, nano nanora!
お菓子の国のお姫様
The princess of Candyland,
とびきりプリティな０歳児
An extra-pretty zero-year-old!
ピアノだって弾けるんだし
I can even play the piano,
赤ちゃんじゃないのらよ！
So I'm not a baby, nora!
ワガママだって言うけれど
You might call me selfish,
ルーナはお姫様なのらから
But Luna is a princess, nora!
ルーナイト達も執事も
My LuKnights and butler alike,
いちいちうるさいのら！
Are always so noisy, nora!
さあ、ルーナイト達！準備はできたのら？
Now, LuKnights! Are you ready, nora?
出陣なのらー！
Time to march, nora~!
パフェもしゅわしゅわも早く用意するのら！
Hurry up and prepare my parfait and soda water, nora!
あれもこれも食べたいのら！
I want to eat this and that, nora!
おいしいのはひとりじめ
I'll keep all the delicious treats to myself,
まずいのや苦いのは
Gross and bitter things,
ルーナイト達に差し入れ！
Are for the LuKnights!
チョコレートの噴水も
A chocolate fountain,
キャンディの首飾りも
And a candy necklace too!
素敵なのたくさんあるのら
There are so many wonderful things, nora.
だからルーナのために
So for Luna's sake,
集めて来てね♡
go collect them all, okay?♡
絶対、絶対、絶対約束！
Promise me, promise me, absolute promise!
なのなのら！
Nano nanora!
まわる まわる まわ ルーナ
Spinning, spinning, spin, Luna!
もっとぐるぐるまわって
Spin even more round and round,
もっともっと
Even more, even more!
ぐるぐるまわって
Spinning round and round,
みんなぐるぐるまわって
Everyone, spin round and round!
ぐるぐるそうやって
Spinning round and round, just like that,
もっとぐるぐるまわって
Spin even more round and round,
ぐるぐるまわって
Spinning round and round,
ずっとぐるぐるまわるーな
Spinning round and round forever, spin, Luna!
ぐるぐる地球は
The spinning Earth...
回り始め幾億年
...began rotating billions of years ago.
いつまでもこのまま
Forever and ever, just like this,
回るみんなに幸せを...
bringing happiness to everyone spinning...
まわりつづくまわルーナ
Keep on spinning, spin, Luna!
ますますます社会がぐるぐるま〜...
More and more, society spins round and r—...
あれ？
Huh?
ぐるぐるまわって
Spinning round and round,
もっとぐるぐるまわって
Spin even more round and round,
ぐるぐるまわって
Spinning round and round,
みんなぐるぐるまわって
Everyone, spin round and round!
ぐるぐる笑って
Laughing round and round,
もっともっと
Even more, even more!
ぐるぐる踊って
Dancing round and round,
みんな踊って
Everyone, dance!
ぐるぐる回って
Spinning round and round,
もっと
Even more!
ぐるぐる
Round and round...
んな～
Nnaaa~
ぐるぐるまわる＠まわルーナ
Spinning and turning, spinning Ruuna!
いつもおとぎ話のお姫様
Always the princess of a fairy tale...
みんなの輝くお月様
And everyone's shining moon...
今日はおやすみして
But tonight, take a rest...
重たい王冠今は置いといて
And put aside the heavy crown for now.
どっちの私も好きになってくれますか
Will you love both versions of me?
どっちも欲しいから まんなかにいたくなる
Since I want both, I want to stay right in the middle!
スニーカーとシャツに着替えて
Changing into sneakers and a shirt,
あるき出したんだ 出発のアラームは
I started walking. The departure alarm...
新しい私が鳴らしてあげる
...will be rung for you by the new me.
両腕をいっぱいにしても
Even if I fill both of my arms,
ぎゅっとしたい この気持ち入らない
I want to hold you tight, but these feelings won't fit.
かたっぽなんて選べない
I can't just choose one side,
迷ってるなら まんなかなんだよ
so if you're lost, the middle is the place to be!
満開の青春
Youth in full bloom,
満腹に摂取
ingesting until full,
満天の流星群
a meteor shower across the whole sky.
満月に heaven
Full moon in heaven,
満面に笑顔にして
putting a big smile on my face,
満点すぎる思い出
memories that deserve a perfect score,
まるまルーナ happy day !!
a completely round Ruuna happy day!!
せかいのまんなかで プリンセスを
Right in the middle of the world, for the princess...
忘れるくらい 胸まんたんにきゅんってしてみたい
I want to feel my heart throb so much it fills my chest.
どっちだっておほの私 瞬きしたら
Either way, it's the real me, so if you blink...
君のどまんなか
...I'll be right in the center of your heart!
まんなかにかさなるちてん
The point overlapping right in the middle.
まんなかでよくばるちてん
The point where I get greedy right in the middle.
まんなかのまんなかちてん
The very center, the middle point.
恋する女の子のいいとこ取りで
Taking the best parts of a girl in love,
照れ隠しと素直の今 まんなかちてん
hiding my shyness and being honest, at the middle point.
跪きなさい。
Kneel down.
汝、この城の扉を叩いた者よ。
Ye who have knocked on the gates of this castle...
誓いなさい。
Take your oath.
このルーナの盾となり矛となり、
To become Luna's shield and sword,
夜はぐっすり眠れるまで、
and until I can fall fast asleep at night,
ともにあることを！
be always by my side!
捧げなさい！ 姫であるぞ！
Offer it up! For I am your princess!
止まるな！ ルーナって？
Don't stop! Who's Luna?
紅茶のカップ がちゃがちゃ 鳴らさないって えらい！
Not clattering your teacup, that's admirable!
スコーンだって こぼさず 綺麗に食べて すごい！
Eating your scones without spilling a single crumb, that's amazing!
たまに王冠 どっちが前か 間違っちゃうの かわいい！
Sometimes putting your crown on backwards, that's so cute!
通ってよし！ なのら 開城！
You may pass, nanora! Open the gates!
ルーナイト 第一条！
LuKnight Rule #1!
誰よりルーナが好きな人！
You must love Luna more than anyone else!
ルーナイト 第二条！
LuKnight Rule #2!
シルクのお布団持ってきて！
Bring me a silk duvet!
ルーナイト 第三条！
LuKnight Rule #3!
三時のお茶会来れる人！
You must attend the 3 PM tea party!
守れなかったら 即制裁！
Failure to comply means immediate punishment!
分かってほしいのら…
I want you to understand, nanora...
これも、帝王学を学ぶため……
This is also to learn the ways of monarchical rule...
愛という名の……
In the name of love...
教育なのら～！
...it is your education, nanora!
守ってルーナイト 想ってくんないと
Protect me, LuKnight! If you don't care about me,
プロムナード ボイコット なのなのら！
I will boycott the promenade, nananora!
手の甲に 忠誠誓うの Chu
Swear your loyalty with a kiss on the back of my hand, Chu!
ガラスの靴履かせてワルツ
Put on my glass slippers and let's waltz!
守ってルーナイト かまってくんないと
Protect me, LuKnight! If you don't pay attention to me,
ブラウニーにキャンディ どれだけあってもね保存中
no matter how many brownies or candies I have,
君がいなきゃだめ！
it's no good without you!
みんな 心して 捧げなさい！
Everyone, prepare your hearts and offer them up!
姫であるぞ！
For I am your princess!
守ってルーナイト 想ってくんないと
Protect me, LuKnight! If you don't care about me,
プロムナード ボイコット なのなのら！
I will boycott the promenade, nananora!
永遠の忠誠 この指に Chu
Swear eternal loyalty with a kiss on this finger, Chu!
ガラスの靴履かせてワルツ
Put on my glass slippers and let's waltz!
守ってルーナイト かまってくんないと
Protect me, LuKnight! If you don't pay attention to me,
ブラウニーにキャンディ どれだけあってもね保存中
no matter how many brownies or candies I have,
君がいなきゃだめ！
it's no good without you!
みんな 心して 捧げなさい！
Everyone, prepare your hearts and offer them up!
姫であるぞ！
For I am your princess!
んな～～～い！
Nnaaa~y!
みんな、おは！
Hello, everyone!
ホロライブ4期生、姫森ルーナなのだ〜！
I am Hololive's 4th Generation, Himemori Luna-nanoda~!
今日はルーナの生誕祭ライブ！
Today is my birthday celebration live!
みんな、来てくれてありがちゅー！
Thank you all so much for coming!
今日のハッシュタグはこちら！
Today's hashtag is right here!
テレン！ ＃姫森ルーナ生誕LIVE2025
Ta-da! #HimemoriLunaBirthdayLIVE2025
これでいっぱいツイートしてください！
Please tweet a lot using this hashtag!
そして、みんな、ルーナの...
And, everyone, Luna's...
の、オリ曲メドレーどうだった？
How was the original song medley?
可愛かった？
Was it cute?
ふむふむ、ふむふむ。可愛い可愛い、分かってたのら。
Hmm hmm, hmm hmm. Cute, cute, I knew it!
そして！今日のステージを見てください！
And now! Please look at today's stage!
だだだだだ、すげえ！雲だらけ！
Dadadadada, awesome! It's full of clouds!
あっちのさ、この雲の向こう、何があるのらな？
Over there, beyond these clouds, I wonder what's there?
みんな予想してみて！
Everyone, try to guess!
そして今日のライブテーマは、ルーナ・リバース・デイです！
And today's live theme is "Luna Reverse Day"!
どんな意味があるのか。はてさて。
What kind of meaning does it have? Let's see.
そして、待ってルーナイト！
And wait, Lu-knights!
歌ってる時に、ルーナたん大変身しました！みんな気づいてくれたのら？
During the singing, Luna-tan went through a big transformation! Did everyone notice?
100万人記念で新モデルになりましたー！
I got a new model to celebrate reaching 1 million subscribers!
そして、おルーナイトが、なんかルーナたんに魔法をかけてくれたのらよね？
And Lu-knights, you cast some magic on Luna-tan, right?
おルーナイト！おる？
Lu-knights! Are you there?
姫！姫！おるよ！姫！ おるよ！どこにいるのら？
Princess! Princess! We're here! Princess! / You are! Where are you?
わあ！この雲の向こうにいます！ おる！そうなのらね。
Whoa! We're beyond this cloud! / You are! I see.
ねえねえ、私の新しい姿、どう？どう？どう？ めちゃくちゃ可愛いよ！ え、本当？
Hey hey, how is my new appearance? / It's incredibly cute! / Oh, really?
せっかくだから、姫の以前の姿をだして比較してみよう！ あ、いいね、いいね！
Since we're here, let's bring out your previous appearance and compare them! / Oh, that's a great idea!
わ、どこどこ。あ、光ってる。出た！パネルが出そう。出た出た出た！
Wow, where where? Oh, it's shining. The panels are coming out. They're out!
え、見てどう？変わった？変わった？ それではまずは、足元から見ていきましょう！ はーい！
Hey, look, what do you think? Did it change? / Well then, first, let's look from the feet! / Okay!
そうそうそうそう。あ、蜘蛛さん。いい感じですよね、これ。 どうだ？どうだ？
Yes yes yes yes. Ah, Spider-san. This looks really nice, doesn't it? / How is it?
なんかこれ影の感じとか変わった？ 変わった？変わった？変わった？
Did the shadow effect or something change here? / Did it change? Did it?
あ、スカートとか、ポスターの感じ変わったね！可愛いね！ およおよ。良い感じ、良い感じ！
Ah, the skirt and the overall textures have changed! It's cute! / Oyo-oyo. Looking good!
あ、待って、ここら辺。ここら辺とかも待って。加圧トレーニングの効果？ え？でてる？でてる？ルーナたん、でてる？
Ah, wait, around here. Is this the effect of pressure training? / Eh? Is it showing? Is it?
最近、加圧トレーニングしてる？ やってるよ！パーソナルだけどな。
Have you been doing pressure training lately? / I am! Though it's personal training.
あ、そうそうそう。後ろ向いて、後ろ、後ろ。 え、後ろ？およ。
Ah, right, right. Turn around, look at the back. / Eh, the back? Oyo.
おおー！これこれ！見て、これ！髪の毛の揺れ！あとシルエットか！これめっちゃ良いじゃん！ そうそうそう。へへへ。
Ohhh! Look at this! The movement of the hair! And the silhouette! This is so good! / Right, right. Hehehe.
そして、ルーナたんの手も見て欲しいのら！
And I want you to look at Luna-tan's hands too!
わあ！おててが小さくて可愛いね！ でしょ。手相も良い感じ。
Wow! Your hands are so small and cute! / Right? The palm lines are good too.
手相、手相ね。うん、うん。 あと、顔も見て、お顔。
Palm lines indeed. Yeah, yeah. / And look at the face, the face.
あ、お顔、このパネルと比べるのちょっと難しいんだけど、斜めから見た時のフェイスラインとか変わったね。凄く可愛いじゃん！ 変わった、変わった。へへへ。パパありがとう！
It's hard to compare, but your facial outline from an angle has changed. You look so cute! / It did, it did. Hehehe. Thank you, Papa!
ぜひみんなもね、過去の3D配信と見比べて欲しいのら！
I definitely want everyone to compare this with past 3D streams!
ねえねえ、ポル、ポルナイト？ おお？
Hey, Pol, Pol-knight? / Oh?
質問があるのだけど、そっちの雲の向こうってどうなってるのら？
I have a question, what is beyond those clouds over there?
舞踏会の会場あるよ。来る？ え！まじ？
There is a ballroom venue. Are you coming? / Eh! Really?
おいでよ、馬車！ え、ば、馬車？ わあ、めっちゃ光ってる！
Come on, the carriage! / Eh, c-carriage? / Wow, it's shining so much!
わ、わ、わ、でけえ！これムーンギャラクシーの時ステージにくっついてた馬車なのらよ！
Wow, wow, wow, it's huge! This is the carriage from Moon Galaxy!
というわけで、姫、乗っちゃってください！ 乗れるの？ 乗ってください！ 乗る、乗る、乗る！
So, Princess, please get on! / I can? / Please get on! / I'll get on!
うわあ！すごい！中も豪華なのら！
Wow! Amazing! The inside is so luxurious too!
ちょっとここ座ってみるのら、よいしょ。ルーナイトの人形もあるのらね！すごい！
Let me try sitting here, yoisho. There's even a Lu-knight doll! Amazing!
姫、準備はオッケーですか？ もちろん！出発進行なのら！
Princess, are you ready? / Of course! Let's depart!
よし、飛びますよ！ いくぞー！
Alright, we're taking off! / Let's go!
動いた！
It moved!
おお、進むぞ！
Oh, we are moving forward!
すげえ、この馬車飛んでるのら！
Awesome, this carriage is flying!
よし、よいしょ、よいしょ、こっち見てみよう。うわあ、すごい！
Okay, yoisho, yoisho, let's look out here. Wow, amazing!
星と雲がめちゃくちゃ綺麗な方ら！
The stars and clouds are so beautiful!
うわあ、眺め最高なのらね！
Wow, the view is the best!
がたんごとんと動いてますわ。良いのら！
It's rattling along. It's nice!
こっちからも見てみるのらね、よいしょ、よいしょ。
Let's look from this side too, yoisho, yoisho.
こっちもすごい、眺め最高！うわあ、良い感じなのら！
This side is amazing too, the best view! Wow, it feels great!
高いな、でもここ。
It's high up here, though.
っておルーナイトさ、このまま進んだら目の前の立派な雲とぶつかるのらけどさ。大丈夫なの、進んで？向こうが何も見えねえのらよ。
Hey, Lu-knights, if we keep going, we'll crash into that big cloud ahead. Is it okay to go forward? I can't see anything on the other side.
姫、ご安心ください！
Princess, please do not worry!
このポルーナイトにお任せあれ！
Leave it all to this Polnight!
姫、少々揺れますぞ！
Princess, it's going to be a bit bumpy!
大丈夫？つかまっててください！
Are you okay? Please hold on!
え、大丈夫？本当にこれ...
Eh, are you sure? Is this really...
いきますぞー！
Here we go!
本当に大丈夫！？
Are you really sure it's okay?!
うわ、待って、雲来てるよ！
Whoa, wait, clouds are coming!
うわー、もう来てる！うわああ！
Whoaaa, they're already here! Whoaaaa!
あたし今 最上級に可愛いの
Right now, I am at my absolute cutest
君に振られて 最上級に可愛いの
Dumped by you, I am at my absolute cutest
これが乙女の逆襲だ！
This is a maiden's counterattack!
もう気づいてるかもしれないけど言うわ
You might have already noticed, but I'll tell you
あたしね 今とても
You see, right now, I am extremely...
可愛い
...cute!
君に始めた恋 君が終わらすなんて
You started this love, so how dare you end it
なんだそれ 泣いちゃうぞ
What the heck is that? I'm gonna cry!
可愛い
But I'm cute!
あたしの連絡だけ
Just my messages...
通知OFFにしてたなんて
...you had them on mute?!
友達から聞いたよ
I heard it from a friend!
連絡しすぎだって
"You message too much," you said
君が不安にさせるからじゃん保存する
but that's only because you make me feel insecure!
もう気にしてないけど
I don't even care anymore,
だって今
because right now...
君に振られて 最上級に可愛いの
Dumped by you, I am at my absolute cutest!
自分史上 一番ときめき放つわ保存する
Unleashing the most excitement in my life!
最上級に可愛いの
At my absolute cutest!
認めなよ これが 乙女の逆襲だ！
Accept it, this is a maiden's counterattack!
さすがに失恋直後は
Naturally, right after a heartbreak...
涙でぐちゃぐちゃで
...I was a crying, messy disaster,
可愛い
...yet still cute!
君が泣かせたのに
Even though you made me cry,
雑なサヨナラだった
it was such a sloppy goodbye.
なんだそれ 泣いちゃうぞ
What the heck is that? I'm gonna cry!
可愛い保存する
But I'm cute!
「二人しか知らない」って
"Only the two of us know this,"
言ってた話だって
you said about that story.
どうしてあの子も知ってるの
So how come that girl knows it too?
「別れてよかった」なんて
Don't make me think...
思わせないでほしかった
..."I'm glad we broke up."
好きだったから
Because I really loved you.
君に振られて 最上級に可愛くなりました
Dumped by you, I became my absolute cutest!
むしろありがとう 最上級に可愛くなったって
If anything, thank you! Tell me I've become my absolute cutest,
ねぇ言って
tell me!
あいつがなんか可愛くなったって
Saying, "She's somehow gotten so cute..."
ねぇ聞いて
hey, listen!
君に振られて 最上級に可愛いの
Dumped by you, I am at my absolute cutest!
自分史上 一番ときめき放つわ
Unleashing the most excitement in my life!
最上級に可愛いの
At my absolute cutest!
認めなよ これが 乙女の逆襲だ！
Accept it, this is a maiden's counterattack!
最上級に可愛いの
At my absolute cutest!
君に振られて 最上級に可愛いの
Dumped by you, I am at my absolute cutest!
あたしひたむきシンデレラ！
I'm a single-minded Cinderella!
退屈な月曜日
A boring Monday,
あなたの香り で目覚めるの
I wake up to your scent.
纏ったトップノート
Wearing the top note,
そうよ 秘密の物語 なの
yes, this is our secret story.
うまくリプライ
I can't reply
できない 震えるハート
very well, with my trembling heart.
ためらい × はじらい ＝ 空回り…
Hesitation x Shyness = Running in circles...
誘うファンタジー 重なっちゃうくらい
An inviting fantasy, so much that they overlap,
一途だもん
because I'm so devoted!
あなたに夢中です
I'm crazy about you!
Ah バズっちゃバズっちゃやぁだ！
Ah, I don't want you going viral, going viral!
ねぇ かまってかまってもっと！
Hey, pay attention, pay attention to me more!
誰もがあなたを狙っちゃう
Everyone is targeting you!
ウインクひとつでメロメロにさせちゃって
Making everyone fall head over heels with a single wink,
こっちの気も知らないで！
completely unaware of how I feel!
もー！バズっちゃバズっちゃやぁだ！
Jeez! I don't want you going viral, going viral!
ねぇ 射抜いて射抜いてずっと！
Hey, shoot through, shoot through my heart forever!
いつでもあなたに翻弄ちゅう
I'm always at your mercy!
あたしひたむきシンデレラ！
I'm a devoted Cinderella!
どんな道が待ってても
No matter what path lies ahead,
ガラスのヒールで駆けてくよ
I'll run through in glass heels.
魔法が解けても
Even if the magic wears off...
覚めない夢を
I'll give you a dream...
あなたにあげる
...that you won't wake up from.
だからぜったい負けない！
So I'll never, ever lose!
脈打つビート
With a beating pulse,
純愛してたい！
I want to love purely!
まっすぐに
Straightforwardly.
想うエンパシー 伝わっちゃうくらい
So much that my feelings of empathy get through,
本気だもん
I'm serious.
まさしく無敵です
I'm truly invincible!
Ah ハマってハマっていいよ
Ah, it's okay to fall, fall for me!
ねえ ディグってディグってきゅんと
Hey, dig, dig and squeeze,
恋する乙女は変幻自在
A girl in love is ever-changing.
「キレイ」も「キューティー」も よくばりに励めば
If I greedily strive for both "beautiful" and "cute,"
輝く自分になるの
I'll become a sparkling me!
さぁ！ハマってハマっていいよ
Come on! It's okay to fall, fall for me!
ねえ 気づいて気づいてちゃんと！
Hey, notice me, notice me properly!
まだまだ乙女は日進月歩
Girls are still making rapid progress.
世界で一番のドキドキがほしいの
I want the best heart-pounding feeling in the world.
あなた いけない プリンスですっ
You are a bad prince!
I Love You!
I Need You!
Ah 「好き」って「好き」ってなんで
Ah, why is it that when we say "I love you, I love you,"
そう ズキってズキっていうの？
It throbs and aches like this?
けなげなココロは困惑中
My pure heart is in confusion.
愛しさふくらんで こんなにも苦しいの
My love swells up, and it hurts so much.
いますぐこっちに微笑って！
Smile at me right now!
Ah バズっちゃバズっちゃやだ
Ah, I don't want to go viral, go viral!
ねえ かまってかまってもっと！
Hey, pay attention, pay attention to me more!
誰もがあなたを狙っちゃう
Everyone is aiming for you.
ウインクひとつでメロメロにさせちゃって
Making me fall head over heels with a single wink,
こっちの気も知らないで！
Without even knowing my feelings!
もー！バズっちゃバズっちゃやだ
Geez! I don't want to go viral, go viral!
ねえ 射抜いて射抜いてずっと！
Hey, shoot through, shoot through my heart forever!
いつでもあなたに翻弄ちゅう
I'm always toyed with by you.
誰よりあなたのトクベツでいたいの
I want to be your special one more than anyone else.
あぁ なんて、ぜいたくかな･･･？許してね
Ah, is that too selfish...? Please forgive me.
あたしひたむきシンデレラ！
I'm a devoted Cinderella!
オトメロディー
Otome Melody
スキスキスー フワフワフー
Suki-Suki-Su, Fuwa-Fuwa-Fu!
こんなキモチ メロメロディ
This kind of feeling is a Mero-Melody.
夢だけど 夢じゃない
It's a dream, but it's not a dream.
お願いね マイメロディ
Please, My Melody.
オトナじゃない オトメです。
I'm not an adult, I'm a maiden.
恋するのが仕事です
Falling in love is my job.
君の名前つぶやくと
When I whisper your name,
ドキドキするの
My heart starts thumping.
聞き分けない この胸が
This stubborn heart of mine
歌い出して止まらない
Starts singing and won't stop.
上手じゃなくてゴメンナサイ
I'm sorry I'm not very good at it,
だけど聞いて
But please listen...
とどけ
...and let it reach you.
マイメロディー マイメロディー
My Melody, My Melody.
星空を越えて
Crossing the starry sky,
君の夢 守るリボン
The ribbon that protects your dreams.
マイメロディー ハート見つけたなら
My Melody, if you find a heart,
グルグル巻きしちゃうからね
I'll wrap it up round and round!
WOW WOW WOW 覚悟しといて
Wow, wow, wow, be prepared!
嘘じゃない
It's not a lie.
オトナじゃない オトメです。
I'm not an adult, I'm a maiden.
泣いたりだってしちゃいます
I might even cry sometimes.
女の子って魔法で
Girls are made...
作られたの
...with magic.
スキスキスー フワフワフー
Suki-Suki-Su, Fuwa-Fuwa-Fu!
こんなキモチ メロメロディ
This kind of feeling is a Mero-Melody.
夢だけど 夢じゃない
It's a dream, but it's not a dream.
お願いね マイメロディ
Please, My Melody.
キライじゃない ってゆーかスキ
I don't hate you, in fact, I love you.
スナオになんてなれません
I can't be honest with myself.
君の笑顔見るだけで
Just looking at your smile,
フニャフニャするの
Makes me go all soft inside.
それなのにー それなのに！
Even so! Even though!
憎まれ口 撃っちまくり
I keep shooting off hateful words,
ひとりになって落ち込んで
And then I get depressed all by myself,
枕パンチ！！
Punching my pillow!
だから
So...
マイメロディー マイメロディー
My Melody, My Melody.
本当の気持ち 風になって結ぶリボン
My true feelings, a ribbon tied by turning into the wind.
マイメロディー 歌えオトメゴコロ
My Melody, sing out, maiden's heart.
来る来る恋 つかまえちゃえ
Catch that love spinning round and round!
Wou wou wou 逃がさないから
Wou wou wou, because I won't let you escape!
ここへ来て
Come over here.
キライじゃない ツライです
I don't hate it, it's just painful!
真っ赤にだってなっちゃいます
I even turn bright red!
女の子って不思議で 作られたの
Girls are made out of mysteries.
とどけ
Reach out!
マイメロディー マイメロディー
My Melody, My Melody!
星空を越えて 君の夢 守るリボン
A ribbon that crosses the starry sky to protect your dreams.
マイメロディー
My Melody!
ハート見つけたら
If I find your heart...
グルグル巻きしちゃうからね
I'm going to wrap it all up!
Wou wou wou 覚悟しといて
Wou wou wou, get ready!
嘘じゃない
It's not a lie.
オトナじゃない オトメです
I'm not an adult, I'm a maiden!
泣いたりだってしちゃいます
I'll even cry sometimes!
女の子って魔法で 作られたの
Girls are made out of magic.
スキスキスー フワフワフー
Suki suki suu, fuwa fuwa fuu,
こんなキモチ メロメロディ
These feelings are a melo-melody!
夢だけど 夢じゃない
It's a dream, but it's not a dream!
お願いね マイメロディ
Please, My Melody!
マイメロディ
My Melody!
はーい！
Yes!
ということで！
And with that!
最上級にかわいいの！と
I just sang "Saijoukyuu ni Kawaii no!",
いっときシンデレラ！
"Ittoki Cinderella",
あと「オトメロディー」
and "Otomelody"!
3曲連続で歌いました！
Three songs in a row!
いぇーい！
Yay!
雲が晴れたステージってこうなってるのねー！
So this is what the stage looks like with the clouds cleared up!
すっごい！でっかい！
Wow! It's huge!
舞踏会みたいなのなのね！
It's like a ballroom!
あ、ここ見て！シャンデリアがあるのなの！
Oh, look at this! There's a chandelier!
ザ・舞踏会、ダンスするって場所になのね！
It really is a ballroom, a place to dance!
あと、お城の上の方ってこうなってたんだ！
Also, the top of the castle looks like this!
見てー！すごい可愛い！
Look! It's so cute!
ほら、これ天窓じゃん！
Look, this is a skylight!
豪華なのなのねー！
It's so luxurious!
すごい！あ、待って！
Awesome! Oh, wait!
Luna RebirthDayの看板もあるのなの！
There's even a "Luna RebirthDay" sign!
今日はLuna RebirthDayだからな！
Because today is my Luna RebirthDay!
見てみてー、すごい可愛い！
Take a look, it's so cute!
お？
Oh?
なんだ？なんだ？なんだ？
What is it? What is it?
最高だったよーー！！
That was awesome!
え？ ルーナイト？
Eh? Lu-Knight?
ルーナイトじゃないか！
It's a Lu-Knight!
え、実はね、姫にはまだ隠された姿が残されているのです！
Actually, Princess, you still have a hidden form left!
え、な、何なのなの？
Eh? Wh-What is it?
ルーナイトの魔法でそのお姿にしてみせましょう！
Let's reveal that form with Lu-Knight magic!
え、え、え、何？何、何、何、何？
Eh? Eh? What? What is it?!
てってれー！
Ta-da!
わー！すごーい！かわいい！
Wow! Awesome! So cute!
新しいヘアスタイルなのなのー！
It's a new hairstyle!
ルーナイトがプレゼントしてくれたのなのね！
The Lu-Knights gave it to me as a present!
よし！じゃあ、
Alright! Then...
この新しい髪型で歌っちゃうのなのー！！
I'll sing with this new hairstyle!
ア・ナ・タのアイドル サインはB
I'm your idol! The sign is B!
(B小町！ フッフー！)
(B-Komachi! Woo-hoo!)
ようやく会えたね 嬉しいね
We finally met, I'm so happy.
待ち遠しくて足をバッタバタしながら
I was kicking my feet, waiting impatiently,
今日楽しみで寝れなかったよ保存
and couldn't sleep because of today!
(オレモー！)
(Me too!)
緊張なんかしてる場合じゃない
There's no time to be nervous!
1分1秒無駄になんてできない
Every single second is too precious to waste!
さあ始めましょう
So, let's begin!
君も 君も 君も お待ちどうさま
You, and you, and you! Thanks for waiting!
手を鳴らせ いらっしゃいませ
Clap your hands, welcome to the show!
「好き」が集まる場所へようこそ
Welcome to the place where love gathers!
日常はクロークの中保存
Leave your daily life in the cloakroom,
ここに来たなら踊らにゃ損 損 損
since you're here, it's a loss if you don't dance!
客席が居ようが 居まいが 関係ない
It doesn't matter if the seats are full or empty!
会場が大きい 小さいとか 気にしない
I don't care if the venue is big or small!
ちゃんと見えてる
I can clearly see...
君のサイリウム
...your penlight.
今はフーーッと吹けば飛ぶような
Right now, it might blow away with a puff,
小さな小さな才能だけど
such a tiny, tiny talent, but...
私を推してくれるのなら
if you support me...
爆レスをあげる
I'll give you a huge response!
アナタのアイドル
Your idol...
サインはB
...the sign is B!
(チュッ)
(Mwah!)
(B小町！ フッフー！)
(B-Komachi! Fuh-fuh!)
あいつは俺が育てたって
I hope in the near future...
近い将来 自慢してほしいよ
...you can boast that you raised me.
こうしちゃいられない
I can't just stay like this!
(ハーイ！ ハーイ！)
(Hi! Hi!)
君と 君と 今を 楽しまなきゃ
I have to enjoy the present with you, and you!
引きこもりも 人見知りも
Even if you're a shut-in or shy...
普段と違う顔見せてよ
...show me a side of you different from usual!
みんな兄弟 調子どうだい
We're all brothers, how's it going?
なりふり構わずに
Without caring how we look...
そう そう そう
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
人に笑われていても 関係ない
Even if people laugh at us, it doesn't matter!
周りがどうとかこうとか 気にしない
I don't care what others say or do!
主張強すぎ
Your glowsticks are shouting so loud...
君のサイリウム
...showing off your presence!
たとえ世界が 私を拒んで
Even if the world rejects me...
ひとりぼっちを感じたとしても
...and I feel all alone...
アナタが味方でいてくれたら
...if you are on my side...
怖いものはないよ
...there is nothing to fear!
(B小町！ フッフー！)
(B-Komachi! Fuh-fuh!)
見てよ 見てよ 何が始まる
Look, look! Something is starting...
君との物語が
...our story is about to unfold!
嗚呼 なんて素晴らしい景色だ！
Ah, what a wonderful sight!
客席が居ようが 居まいが関係ない
Whether the seats are full or empty, it doesn't matter!
会場が大きい 小さいとか気にしない
I don't care if the venue is big or small!
ちゃんと見えてる
I can clearly see...
君のサイリウム
...your glowsticks shining!
今はふーっと吹けば 飛ぶような
Right now, it's so fragile it could blow away...
小さな小さな才能 だけど
...it's just a tiny, tiny talent, but...
私を推してくれるのなら
If you support me...
アナタが味方でいてくれたら
...and if you are on my side...
爆レスをあげる
...I'll give you a huge response!
アナタのアイドル
Your idol...
サインはB
...the sign is B!
(フッフー！)
(Fuh-fuh!)
結婚しようなー！
Marry me!
ロマンスの不祥事 逃がさない
I won't let any romantic scandal slide!
消してあげる
I'll erase it for you...
シル・ヴ・プレジデント
...s'il vous, President!
宣誓！私が大統領になったら
I swear! If I become the President...
人の男にちょっかいかける女は島流しにします
...any girl who flirts with another's man will be exiled!
宣誓！私が大統領になったら
I swear! If I become the President...
いやただの友達だよ〜って誤魔化す奴は 臍から電気を流します
...those who try to brush it off as 'just friends' will get shocked through their belly buttons!
だ・だ・だ・大胆不敵 センセーショナルクローズアップ
D-D-D-Daring, fearless, sensational close-up!
D.D.D.Don't cry
やるぜ徹底的にリサーチだ
I'll do a thorough investigation!
大嫌い？ しょうがない？
Hate them? Can't help it?
クズは病気ね バイバイ・バイ
Scum is a disease, so bye-bye-bye!
権力！ 財産！ 地位名誉！！
Power! Wealth! Status and fame!!
なんにもないけど裁きたいでしょ？
We have none of that, but we still want to judge, right?
1 2 3
だ・だ・だ・大統領になったらね
...if I become the President...
まずは君を捕まえるね
...first, I'll lock you up!
濡れたタオルで
With a wet towel...
洗いざらい吐かせるね
...I'll make you spill everything!
誰ですかあの子（にゃあ〜）
Who is that girl? (Meow~)
ダメですかそうですか
Is it a no-go? I see...
(あちゃ〜)
(Oh dear~)
ロマンスの不祥事 逃がさない
I won't let any romantic scandal slide!
消してあげる
I'll erase it for you...
しろ・ヴ・ぷれぷれ プレジデント
S-S-S'il vous, President!
宣誓！私が大統領になったら
I swear! If I become the President...
ただの仕事の付き合いだよ？って言う奴は 二度と働けなくしてやります合
...anyone who says 'it's just a business meeting' will never work again!
宣誓！以下略！
I swear! Et cetera!
いや向こうが強引でさぁって言う男の口には レジンを流し込んで固めてやります
...any guy who says 'she forced herself on me' will have his mouth filled with resin!
み・み・密着 まるでドン・ファン気取りスキャンダラス
C-C-Close contact, a scandalous Don Juan wanna-be!
ま・ま・まったん 価格解消なしのスクープね
E-E-End of the line, a scoop with no price cut!
愛はない？ 理由じゃない
No love? That's no excuse!
悪くないのね はい はい はい
You did nothing wrong? Sure, sure, sure!
軽薄！ ノーノー！ イケシャシャ！
Frivolous! No, no! Shameless!
なんにもないとかありえないでしょ？
Saying 'nothing happened' is impossible, right?
1 2 3
だ・だ・だ・大統領になってもね
...even if I become the President...
たぶん君は変わらないね
...you probably won't change!
しらっととぼけて
Feigning ignorance...
のらりくらりかわすのね
...and dodging it casually!
デートですか今晩は（うわぁ〜）
Is it a date tonight? (Whoa~)
本気ですかそうですか
Are you serious? I see...
(ほらぁ〜)
(See~)
情熱とは不注意 微熱も
Passion is carelessness, and even a slight fever...
消してしまいたい
...I want to erase it completely!
ワン、ツー、スリー！
One, two, three!
だ・だ・だ・大統領になったらね
If I... I... I become the president,
マジで君を捕まえるね
I'm seriously going to capture you.
濡れたタオルで
With a wet towel...
洗いざらい吐かせるね
I'll make you spit out everything!
ど・ど・ど！
Do, do, do!
どこですか 今あんた
Where are you right now?
見っけちゃった バレちゃった
Found you! You're busted!
夜道にはご用心 さよなら
Be careful on the night roads. Goodbye...
代わりに銃声
...and in its place, a gunshot!
しる・ヴ・ぷれぷれ ぷれじでんと
S'il vous ple-ple-president!
電波テンポアップして絶賛感電中！
Boosting the signal tempo, highly charged right now!
あなたにも忘れたいこと
Is there something you want to forget too,
悲しいことあるのかしらね
some sad memory you might have?
知らない映画なのに涙を流すのは
Crying over a movie I don't even know...
ドラマチックが足りてないからよ
It's because there's not enough drama in my life.
そんな愚にも付かないこと
Thinking about such useless things,
くだらないこと考えてばかりね
just constantly dwelling on trivial matters...
雨が上がれば愛もその横顔も
Once the rain clears up, love and that profile of yours
誰かのものになるのでしょう
will probably belong to someone else.
嘘っぱちのファンデーションも全部
Even this phony makeup, all of it,
今夜のためよ
is all for tonight.
なのに一体全体どうして
Yet, why on earth...
どうして何故何故のハテナ
Why is it always a mystery of "why" and "how"?
不安定なカンテラ何処まで行くの
With an unstable lantern, how far will we go?
あなた一切合切放り去ってもう
Since you've thrown everything away already,
冗談じゃないわ
you've got to be kidding me!
トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous!
その時が来たって如何にもならないぜ
Even when the time comes, there's nothing we can do.
曖昧な本当なんてメランコリー化するだけ
Vague truths only turn into melancholy.
あたしをさあ掻っ攫って今テイクオンミー
So come and sweep me away, take on me right now!
あー、ちゃんちゃらおかしいな法度ばかり
Ah, nothing but ridiculously absurd rules,
食指がぴくりともしないわ
they don't tempt me even one bit.
実態の無い感情放っておいたって
Even if I ignore these formless feelings,
策略なんてありゃあせんのに何故
there's no hidden strategy, so why?
あーもう懲り懲りよ
Ah, I've had absolutely enough of this.
あたしの喝となる気質もじっと堪えて取り繕っては
Holding back and dressing up my fiery personality,
とうとう臨界点
I've finally reached my breaking point.
年がら年中リップサービス鈍感カマしては辟易
Year-round lip service and playing dumb has left me fed up.
どんがらがっしゃんフィールガールは涙の目にも鬼
Crash-and-burn feel girl, even with teary eyes, is like a demon.
今や頭の中のミュージックのせいで
Right now, because of the music in my head,...
あなたの話は一向に聞き取れない
...I can't hear a single thing you're saying.
少しは真当なこと言って
Say something that actually makes sense.
回り出したターンテーブル
The turntable has started to spin,
ねえ全部忘れさせてよ
hey, make me forget everything!
だけど一体全体どうしてどうして何故何故のハテナ
Yet, why on earth, why is it always a mystery of "why" and "how"?
不安定なカンテラ消えない侭ね
The unstable lantern just won't go out, will it?
あなた一口両舌食い違ってもう
With your double-tongued excuses clashing,
冗談じゃないわ
you've got to be kidding me!
トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous!
その時が来たって如何にもならないぜ
Even when the time comes, there's nothing we can do.
曖昧な本当なんてメランコリー化するだけ
Vague truths only turn into melancholy.
あたしを今…
Me, right now...
冗談じゃないわ
You've got to be kidding me!
トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous!
その時が来たって如何にもならないぜ
Even when the time comes, there's nothing we can do.
不甲斐ないわ感情なんてランドリーで落とすだけ
How pathetic, feelings can just be washed away in the laundry.
どうしようともただ
No matter what happens,
あたしと確かめ合いたいだけよ街
I just want to confirm things with you, city.
藍、哀、愛、厭
Indigo, sorrow, love, aversion...
トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous!
その時が来たって如何にもならないぜ
Even when the time comes, there's nothing we can do.
曖昧な本当なんてメランコリー化するだけ
Vague truths only turn into melancholy.
あたしをさあ掻っ攫って今テイクオンミー
So come and sweep me away, take on me right now!
イエス
Yes!
二酸化炭素をはきだして
Exhaling carbon dioxide,
あの子が呼吸をしているよ
that child is breathing.
どん天模様の空の下
Underneath a cloudy, overcast sky,
つぼみのままでゆれながら
swaying gently while still a bud.
野良犬はぼくの骨くわえ
A stray dog carries my bone in its mouth,
野性の力をためしてる
testing its wild, raw power.
路地裏に月がおっこちて
The moon falls down into the back alley,...
犬の目玉は四角だよ
...and the dog's eyes are square.
今日 人類がはじめて
Today, for the very first time, humanity...
木星についたよ
...has reached Jupiter!
ピテカントロプスになる日も
The day we become pithecanthropus...
近づいたんだよ
...has drawn so close.
アラビヤの笛の音響く
The sound of Arabian flutes echoes
街のはずれの夢のあと
At the remains of a dream on the edge of town
つばさをなくしたペガサスが
A Pegasus that lost its wings
夜空にはしごをかけている
Is leaning a ladder against the night sky
武器をかついだ兵隊さん
The soldiers carrying weapons
南にいこうとしてるけど
Are trying to head south, but
サーベルの音はチャッチャラと
The clatter of their sabers
街の空気を汚してる
Is polluting the town air
今日 人類がはじめて
Today, for the first time, humanity
木星についたよ
Reached Jupiter
ピテカントロプスになる日も
The day we become Pithecanthropus
近づいたんだよ
Has drawn near
歌を忘れたカナリア
The canary that forgot its song
牛を忘れた牛小屋
The cowshed that forgot the cows
こわれた磁石をひろい集める
Gathers broken magnets, the doctor
博士はまるはげさ
Is completely bald
あの子は花火を打ち上げて
That child shoots up fireworks
この日が来たのを祝ってる
Celebrating the arrival of this day
冬の花火は強すぎて
The winter fireworks are too strong
ぼくらの体はくだけ散る
Our bodies are shattered to pieces
ブーゲンビリアの木の下で
Under the bougainvillea tree
ぼくはあの子を探すけど
I look for that child, but
月の光にじゃまされて
Obstructed by the moonlight
あの子のカケラはみつからない
I can't find a single piece of them
今日 人類がはじめて
Today, for the first time, humanity
木星についたよ
Reached Jupiter
ついたー！
We arrived!
ピテカントロプスになる日も
The day we become Pithecanthropus
近づいたんだよ
Has drawn near
今日 人類がはじめて
Today, for the first time, humanity
木星についたよ
Reached Jupiter
ついたー！
We arrived!
ピテカントロプスになる日も
The day we become Pithecanthropus
近づいたんだよ
Has drawn near
さるにはなりたくない
I don't want to become a monkey
こわれた磁石を砂浜で
Just gathering broken magnets
ひろっているだけさ
On the sandy beach
今日 人類がはじめて
Today, for the first time, humanity
木星についたよ
Reached Jupiter
ピテカントロプスになる日も
The day we become Pithecanthropus
近づいたんだよ
Has drawn near
さるになるよ
We're becoming monkeys
あー
Ah...
朝まで踊る 夢だけ見せて
Let me dream of dancing until morning
時計の鐘が解く魔法
The magic broken by the clock's chime
曖昧な指 誘う階段
Your vague fingers lead me down the stairs
三段飛ばしに跳ねていく
As I leap down three steps at a time
馬車の中で 震えてた
Inside the carriage, I was trembling
みじめな古着 めくり廻れ
Spinning round in my miserable old clothes
夜の舞踏
At this night ball
見知らぬ顔 探す
Searching for an unfamiliar face
囁くあの声が
That whispering voice...
握り締めた刃 突き立て
thrusts the clenched blade,
すべてを奪えと
to take everything...
孤児集う城
An orphan-gathering castle,
笑み仮面に描いて
painting a smile on my mask.
偽りの慈しみさえ
Even false mercy,
羽で包む 熾天使
wrapped in feathers like a seraph.
灰の中で
In the ashes,
赤く溶けて混じる 硝子の靴
melting and mixing red, the glass slipper.
今更帰る 震えているの
To go back now... I'm trembling.
あなたが目をやる時計
You look towards the clock,
靴脱ぎ踊る スロープ抜けて
dancing with my shoes off, going down the slope.
喉まで伸びる指の先で
With the tips of my fingers reaching to your throat...
すくう雫 口づけて
scooping up the drop, I kiss it.
走る衝動
A running impulse,
背骨抜けていく刹那
the moment it shoots up my spine.
鐘は鳴らさないで
Don't ring the bell,
あなたにひざまずき
kneeling to you.
まだダメと叫んだ 右手が
My right hand that cried, "Not yet!"
突き刺すサヨナラ
thrusts a goodbye.
消せない硝煙を
Un-erasable gunsmoke,
香水にまとう姫
a princess clad in perfume.
強い瞳 僕の凍った
Those strong eyes shoot through...
仮面ごと撃ち抜く
my frozen mask entirely.
今も耳にあなたの吐息が
Even now, your breath in my ear...
突き刺さるの遠い夢
...thrusts like a distant dream.
ステンドグラスごし
Through the stained glass,
光る月が
the shining moon,
君にかぶせたベール
a veil draped over you.
ドレス膝で裂いて
Tearing the dress at the knees,
ティアラは投げ捨てて
throwing the tiara aside.
見つめあう瞳と瞳が
Our eyes locking with one another,
火花を放つ
releasing sparks.
孤独な魂が
Our lonely souls
炎あげ惹かれあう
catch fire and draw together.
その涙すくえないなら
If I cannot scoop away those tears,
まるで一人遊び
it is just like playing alone.
時よ止まれ今は
Stop, oh time! Right now,
あなたに酔いしれて
I'm intoxicated by you.
揺れる鼓動一つ一つを
Every single swaying heartbeat,
刻み付けてたい
I want to carve them deep inside.
とどまれ熱く濡れ
Stay, hot and drenched,
打ち付ける昂まりに
striking against this rising surge.
これ以上は動けないよ
I cannot move any more than this,
まるで御伽噺
it is just like a fairy tale.
みんなー！
Everyone!
ここからはー、大事な、告知たいむなのだー！
From here on, it's time for some important announcements!
ぽるぽるはそこで、見ててなのだね！
Polpol, make sure to watch from right over there!
では、まずは、こちら！
Now, first up is this!
姫森ルーナ誕生日記念2025のグッズが出ます！
The Himemori Luna Birthday Celebration 2025 merch is here!
ではね、こちら詳細、見ていきましょう。
Now then, let's take a look at the details.
ふたりのルーナ♡アクリルジオラマスタンドなのだ！
The "Two Lunas" Acrylic Diorama Stand!
イラストは、ソイルン先生に描いていただきました！
The illustration was drawn by Soirun-sensei!
前のね、髪型と、今回のルーナのね、新しい髪型のルーナが
It features Luna with her previous hairstyle and Luna with her new hairstyle!
そして、今回の生誕ライブのステージに、登場しました！
And they both appear on the stage of this birthday live!
こちらはね、立体的なパーツが、華やかで、可愛い、素敵な、豪華仕様のジオラマスタンドになっております！
It's a gorgeous 3D diorama stand with vibrant, cute, and wonderful parts!
そして、次はこちら！
And next is this!
姫森ルーナぬいぐるみ♡守ってルーナイトver.！
The Himemori Luna Plushie: Protect Me, Lunight Ver.!
はい、届きましたー！
Yes, it has arrived!
はーい！
Hiya!
守ってルーナイトの衣装のんなたんがぬいぐるみになりました！
Nnatan in her "Protect Lu-Knight" outfit has become a plushie!
イェーイ！
Yay!
ぜひぜひみんなお家にお迎えして、んなたんをね、守ってほしいのらよ！
Please welcome me into your home and protect Nnatan, nora!
そして、次はこちら！
And next is this!
デデン！
Ta-da!
ルーナイト2wayバッグ！
Lu-Knight 2-Way Bag!
さっきのぬいぐるみもすっぽり入ってしまうルーナイトがアピールできるバッグになっております！
It's a bag where you can show off your Lu-Knight pride, and the plushie from earlier fits perfectly inside!
バッグはね、なんとリュックにもなって、超便利！
This bag can also be used as a backpack, which is super convenient!
デザインに使用されているモチーフは、ルーナイト由来のもので統一しているので、バッグモードでもリュックモードでも、お好きな方で使ってください！
The motifs used in the design are all based on Lu-Knights, so please use it as a bag or backpack, whichever you prefer!
次はこちら！
Next is this!
デデン！
Ta-da!
ルーナイトカードホルダー！
Lu-Knight Card Holder!
ルーナイト型のカードホルダーです！
It's a Lu-Knight-shaped card holder!
チェキ風カードやホロカのカードも入れられちゃうので、ルーナイトのみんなはこっちもしっかり守ってくださいね！
You can put instax-style cards or Hololive Official Card Game cards inside, so Lu-Knights, make sure to protect this well!
そして、次はこちら！
And next is this!
デデン！
Ta-da!
ASMRボイス「舞踏会の帰り道」
ASMR Voice "On the Way Home From the Ball"
ま、今回はね、舞踏会をイメージした生誕祭ライブなので、ルーナイトと帰路についたひとときをボイスにしました！
Well, since this birthday live is themed around a ball, I made a voice pack about spending time heading home with a Lu-Knight!
馬車の中という密室で、なんか急接近とかしちゃうかも？
In the private space of a carriage, maybe we'll get unexpectedly close?
ということで、最後に改めて、フルセットを見てみましょう！
So, let's take another look at the full set at the end!
こちらフルセット購入特典は…
The bonus for purchasing the full set is...
デデン！
Ta-da!
オリジナルカード！
Original Card!
イラストはソイルン先生で、
With illustration by Soirun-sensei,
表面がチェキ風のカードになってます！
the front side is an instax-style card!
裏面は招待状風のデザインになっていてオシャレなのら！
The back features a stylish invitation-style design, nora!
そして、通常バージョンのフルセット購入特典は、箔押し複製サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカード！
And the bonus for the standard version full set is an instax-style bromide card with a duplicated foil-stamped signature!
そして、数量限定バージョンのフルセット購入特典は、直筆サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードなのら！
And the bonus for the limited-quantity version full set is a handwritten autographed instax-style bromide card, nora!
みんなゲットしてほしいのら！
I want everyone to get it, nora!
グッズはね、配信終了後、販売開始です！
The merch will be on sale after the stream ends!
そして、そして、もう1つ、大事なお知らせがあります！
And there's one more important announcement!
こちら！
This one!
んなっしょいぱっしょん！
Nnasshoi Passion!
こちらをね、この後、歌わせていただきます！
I will be singing this song next!
みんなね、大好きな「んなっしょい」っていう言葉を使っているのでね、
Since it uses everyone's favorite word, "Nnasshoi,"
みんなこの後いっぱい、んなっしょいしてのら！
please say "Nnasshoi" a lot during it, nora!
この配信が終わったら、MVも公開されます！
Once this stream ends, the MV will also be released!
そして、MV公開後も、音源配信が今回初めてやることになったので、こちらもお楽しみに！
Also, the song's digital release will be out right after the MV, so please look forward to it!
ではね、歌います！
Now then, I'm going to sing!
んなっしょいぱっしょん！
Nnasshoi Passion!
べつにオチとかねぇのら！
There’s no punchline or anything nora!
むにゃいむにゃい目をこする
Rubbing my sleepy, sleepy eyes
囚われた城にパーフェキめな朝
In the captive castle, a wonderfully clear morning
んないっ！ んないっ！ お布団を飛び出して海へ行こう
Nnait! Nnait! Jump out of the futon and let's head to the sea
神様だって間違えるんだって
Even gods make mistakes, you know
よくある話だそうです
It’s a common story, or so they say
姫様にね見とれちゃうんだって
Falling under the spell of the Princess
やれやれなのらね
Good grief, nora
夢を夢見て
Dreaming of dreams,
恋に恋して生きていたいから
falling in love with love, I want to live like that, so
これでいいのら！
This is just fine nora!!
んななな泣きたい→笑いたい
Nn-na-na-na · Want to cry -> Want to laugh
心だってうりゃって変えるのら！
Even my heart can be changed with a "urya!" nora!
だから「会いたい」その願いに
So for that wish of "I want to see you"
いま約束の合言葉いくよ
Here comes our promised password, let's go!
んなっしょい！
Nnasshoi!!
まどろみもホラーな夜もあるけどでもね
There are dozy moments and scary nights too, but still
んなっしょい！
Nnasshoi!!
いつまでもみんなおりゅから平気
Everyone's always here with me, so it's okay
まだ遊び足りねぇのら！
We haven't played nearly enough yet nora!
暗い 暗い 夜の中
In the dark, dark night,
ティアラを外して 城を抜けたら
if I take off my tiara and slip out of the castle...
深い 深い 海に出て
and head out to the deep, deep sea...
...バレてんのら ぐっどないとー
...if they found out, then good night!
姫様はね わがまま～なんて
They say princesses are selfish,
おとぎの話よ そうでしょう？
but that's just a fairy tale, right?
何がなんだって わたしなんだって
No matter what, I am who I am.
これでいいのら！！
This is fine!
んな・な・な・なりたい わたしでいたい！
I-I-I-I want to become... I want to be myself!
どこへだって向かってゆけるのら！
I can head anywhere!
「ならば、しゃーない」この想いに
"If so, there's no helping it!" To these feelings,
いま許される合言葉 いくよっ！
now comes the allowed password. Here we go!
んなっしょい！！
Nnasshoi!!
サンゴ礁 白い砂浜も綺麗 そこに
The coral reefs and white sandy beaches are beautiful too. Right there,
んなっしょい！！ 輝くわたし
Nnasshoi!! Shining me!
Q. 帰る理由は？
Q: What's the reason to go back?
A. そこになければねぇのら！
A: If it's not there, there isn't one!
んなああああい！
Nnaaaaai!
りぴーとあふたみ～
Repeat after me~
んなっしょい！んなっしょい！せーのっ！
Nnasshoi! Nnasshoi! Ready, set, go!
(んなっしょい！ んなっしょい！)
(Nnasshoi! Nnasshoi!)
もう1回！
One more time!
(んなっしょい！ んなっしょい！)
(Nnasshoi! Nnasshoi!)
いいねぇ
Nice!
熱い視線が集中
Hot gazes are concentrating,
ハラハラするこころに無我夢中
crazy about my throbbing heart,
だから だから
so, so...
これでいいのら！！
This is fine!
んな・な・な・泣きたい → 笑いたい
I-I-I-I want to cry... but wait, I want to laugh!
こころだって奪ってあげるのら！
I will steal your heart!
だから「会いたい」その願いに
So, "I want to see you." To that wish,
いま約束の合言葉 いくよっ！
now comes the promised password. Here we go!
んなっしょい！！
Nnasshoi!!
まどろみもホラーな夜もあるけど でもね
There are drowsy and scary nights too, but you know,
んなっしょい！！ この先もみんな
Nnasshoi!! From here on out, everyone,
おりゅから平気
I'm here, so it's fine.
まだ遊び足りねぇのら！
I still haven't played enough!
生誕ライブ見に来てくれてありがのら～！！
今年は体調不良の時期だったから
声が出てなかったかもしれない…TOT
[Letter] Thank you so much for coming to see my birthday live concert~!!
Since I was feeling unwell earlier this year,
my voice might not have come out well... TOT
でも最後まで頑張ったのら！！うりゃぁ！！
これからもずっと姫様に仕える忠誠心をな
I Love You ちゅばちゅば (・o・ %)
[Letter] But I did my absolute best until the end!! Uryaa!!
Keep showing your eternal loyalty to the princess, okay?
I Love You, chuba-chuba (・o・ %)